Viktoriia Romaniuk

Phone: (647) 922 6404 (Mobile)

(647) 556 1686 (Home)

Email: <u>romviki@gmail.com</u>

Address: 32 Great Gabe Crescent,

Oshawa, ON, L1L0G6, Canada

Summary

Energetic Group Fitness Instructor and professional choreographer with more than 15 years of experience in the Sport, Fitness and Dance. Opened to innovations, creative and focused on client satisfaction.

Fitness proficiencies

- Strength training
- Pilates
- Aerobic Conditioning
- Training Special Populations
- Sport Specific Training

- Fitness Program Development
- Client Education and Motivation
- Individual Assessment and Planning
- Interpersonal skills

Experience

Private school, Kiev 9/2006 to 7/2010

Group Fitness Instructor, Choreographer

Design and deliver dance classes at primary and secondary school.

Teaching and developing students in all types of dance.

Choreographing and directing dance performances.

Zumba classes

Bodyjam

Gym Olympian, Odessa 8/2000 to 8/2005

Group Fitness Instructor, Choreographer

Training variety of classes such as Flexibility training, Cardio interval training, Body step, Personal training, Pilates.

Develop programs for professional athletes, Youth League, based on their needs Choreographed programs for skaters.

Fitness club, Odessa 9/1995 to 6/2000

Group Fitness Instructor

Delivering variety of classes for different levels and age groups such as Shaping, Aerobic.

Education and Training

- Canfitpro Group Fitness Instructor
- CPR certification

Choreography diploma at Odessa College of Arts, Ukraine

Bachelors Degree in Fine Arts in Dance

• Bilingual Russian/English